hey what's going on everybody my name is
mang I'm back in my barber shop today
we're gonna do another product review
let's get it
[Music]
what's going on everybody my name is
mang I'm back in my barber shop today
I'm going to be doing another product
review I've been getting a lot of
requests to do this hair styling powder
I hear a lot of good things about it but
I have not used it myself so we're going
to be doing this product and we're also
going to do their light work styling gel
too literally just got this in the mail
today so I haven't even opened it up to
take a look uh let's go ahead and open
up this one just to see okay it looks
like it is a light to medium hold all
right and
um
smells pretty good not too strong
and the texture of it is uh clay clay
clay it's Clay a few moments later
playing
clay
anyways not not too bad
okay let's go ahead and open this
package and see what this powder is all
about
so in the Box
there's only
the powder itself I actually watched the
video on this and
supposedly the bottle is only half full
so let me open it up and uh confirm if
it or or isn't
so this is rubber piece here I'm just
gonna
yank off if I can but it does feel
pretty light though okay so I just
removed it and yes
I don't know if you guys can see in
there or not but it literally is only
half
full
first impressions of it it is
um like baby powder
it's very fine
okay so um I have my hair dryer here
we're gonna go ahead and apply some heat
uh style it to make it sound a little
easier and then add the powder and we'll
go from there
[Applause]
so I had my hair down all day so
hopefully that helped a little bit
okay looks like again it wants to split
on the uh 60 40 naturally so we're gonna
go ahead and do that we're gonna add it
straight to the hair
and see
oh yeah it's just like
adding baby powder to your hair now I
heard that if you add a little too much
your hair gets really
um hard to work with so I'm just going
to add a little bit at a time
now I don't even know how this works
like
well that's too much
okay I think that's I think that's
plenty okay let's see if we can push it
back a little bit okay
all right
oh
my hair all tingly I mean
look at that look at that
made my hair
um
tingly
there we go all right let's see if we
can comb this out all right
now it actually does hold my hair pretty
well
it does hold my hair pretty well you
know for uh having
for being a powder
it's not bad and it feels really light
you know kind of like um kind of like um
oh there's a lot of texture on my hands
it feels like chalk my hands on honestly
um this texture feels just like when
you're adding hairspray to your hair and
then you comb it out it's exact same
feeling
not bad
let's do the shake tests
okay
and
I just need to run my hand through it
again
to style it again so not bad not bad at
all it is a really light hold
uh
four days where you're not like
you're trying but you're not really
trying you know what I mean
so
okay okay
now you're supposed to add a little bit
of hairspray to this as well
when you get done but I think I think
this is it for that's all I can do with
this
all I can do with this
okay so let me go uh clean this off and
then let's use the light work okay so
we're back
um we're going to
now try the the light work again it is a
medium to light hold and it does say
that it is a matte finish so this
shouldn't be any shine to it
um I I do have a little bit of the hair
styling powder in there I didn't use any
shampoo just straight up water left a
little texture in there but uh it should
make it easier to style so let's go
ahead and check this out okay so again
the texture itself is like
um
yogurt honestly
okay so uh let's maybe that's a little
too much but we'll see we'll see
spread that across my whole Palms
and run it from the back
to the front so my trouble area is my
sides so I just want to see how oh this
does smell good
can't lie it does smell good
Okay so
just pushing the sides back
I might need a little bit more the front
okay so just a little bit more
[Music]
supposed to be an all-day hold and it's
supposed to be a very light hold but not
bad you know it's pretty good uh if we
go for the let me see let me comb it out
a little bit
okay
hmm
it definitely does
it definitely does do the job it's
actually holding my hair up really well
um
it's a nice
feel to it on my hair it doesn't feel it
doesn't really feel oily or anything
like that at all it is and it does smell
really nice smells good the texture is
good the hold is light but if you're
going for if you want a lighter look a
more flurry look I think this will be
perfect for that
okay let's do let's go ahead and do the
shake tests
oh okay
okay
there we go
not bad at all it held it
it held it
and so let's say let's say my kid comes
up and messes up my hair like they
always do
um it's gonna rub my hand through it
again
and
presto
okay yeah come over here there we go all
right
and the sides are holding up pretty well
so the powder a little weird
um gonna have to get some uh getting
used to but uh not bad overall uh I
would recommend this for like um if you
have longer hair you want some texture
or some volume in this I think that the
hair powder will be perfect for that if
you're looking for a really really light
hole but no shine at all that's going to
hold up all day long uh this works
perfectly so highly recommended uh this
light work from stick gorilla so
so this is it for this product review I
hope you guys enjoyed it if you guys did
please like subscribe and share if you
guys already haven't and if there's
another product out there that you want
me to review please drop them in the
comment below and I'll see what I can do
until next time peace